Keep the door closed...
Cranston Academy: Monster Zone is a animation, adventure,
science fiction film directed by Leopoldo Aguilar.
An intelligent 15-year-old high school student is unexpectedly transferred to a
boarding school where he opens a portal of monsters from another dimension.
Danny (Voice), played by Jamie Bell.
Liz (Voice), played by Ruby Rose.
Mothman, played by Idzi Dutkiewicz.
Ms. Evans, played by Ellie Piercy.
Professor Stern, played by Terry Mynott.
Cranston Academy: Monster Zone (formerly Scary Show) is an animated
horror-comedy film directed by Leopoldo Aguilar.
Produced by Ánima and Prime Focus World, the film is directed by Leopoldo
Aguilar and features the voices of Jamie Bell and Ruby Rose.
The film was first released in Portugal on March 12, 2020, and later in Mexico on June 26, 2020,
featuring the Spanish voices of Polo Morín, Natalia Téllez, and Edson Zuñiga.
The film was later released in the U.S.
by Grindstone Entertainment under the title Monster Zone.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.